JAMES OLUWALEYE



SUMMARY



Meticulous web developer with over 2 years of front end experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach. Implemented new responsive website approach which increased mobile traffic by 20%.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Front-end developer intern

FEB 2022-AUG 2022

FAAN Headquarters

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.

Freelancer

Jul 2022- Present

FIVERR. UPWORK

- Creating web and mobile applications
- Maintaining, optimizing, troubleshooting, and improving websites and mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Maintaining, optimizing, troubleshooting, and improving websites

PROJECTS



- Weather web application
- Insurance website
- FCHBM church website
- Movie Application with RapidApi
- App store redesign
- Cloud Management website

FRONT END DEVELOPER

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ james-oluwaleye-973b32189
- Jamesoluwaleye@gmail.com
- **C** +2347045380644

PORTFOLIO github.com/Ja10th

RELEVANT SKILLS

- CSS and JS Frameworks (e.g., REACT JS, Tailwind, Bootstrap)
- JavaScript
- HyperText Markup Language (HTML)
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- CSS Preprocessors (e.g., Sass)
- Version Control (e.g. Git)
- Responsive Design & Mobile-First Websites
- Technical Skills
- Excellent Communication Skills
- Time Management Skills

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering - BEng ESKU, Nigeria

2017-2022 (ongoing)

CS50 Computer Science (Harvard Online Course)

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

ALX Engineering Program

Aug 2022 - Jul 2022